They'll die when they're dead.
Expend4bles is a action, adventure, thriller film directed by Scott Waugh.
Armed with every weapon they can get their hands on and the skills to use them, The Expendables are the world’s
last line of defense and the team that gets called when all other options are off the table.
But new team members with new styles and tactics are going
to give “new blood” a whole new meaning.
Lee Christmas, played by Jason Statham.
Drew "Easy Day" Farrell, played by 50 Cent.
Gina, played by Megan Fox.
Gunner Jensen, played by Dolph Lundgren.
Decha, played by Tony Jaa.
Rahmat, played by Iko Uwais.
Expend4bles (also known as The Expendables 4) is a 2023 American
action film and the fourth in The Expendables film series.
The film stars an ensemble cast, including Jason Statham, Sylvester Stallone, Curtis "50 Cent"
Jackson, Megan Fox, Dolph Lundgren, Tony Jaa, Iko Uwais, Randy Couture and Andy Garcia.
It was directed by Scott Waugh and written by Kurt
Wimmer, Tad Daggerhart and Max D.
Expend4bles was released in China on September 15, 2023, and in
the United States a week later, by Lionsgate.
The film received negative reviews from critics and grossed $51 million worldwide
against a budget of $100 million, making it a box-office bomb.
It was nominated for seven Golden Raspberry Awards, winning two, for
Worst Supporting Actor and Worst Supporting Actress.
The film explores themes of sequel, nuclear bomb, cargo ship, ring.
The tone is intense.